欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
马蒂
Marty?
有很多顾客在休息室等候
There are customers waiting in the lounge
可没人帮他们把车开来
and no one bringing their cars around.
我知道 爸爸 洛厄尔今早刚辞职
Yeah, I know, Dad. Lowell just quit this morning.
毫不意外
Of course he did.
这年头想留住员工真难
It is impossible to keep employees these days.
你们这一代小年轻没人想工作
Nobody in your generation wants to work.
其实吧 他辞职是因为他卖了一个电影剧本
Actually, he quit because he sold a movie script
给奥普拉的公司但你说的没错
to Oprah's company, but yeah.
如果他是在我这里工作时摸鱼写的
Well, if he wrote it while he was working here,
那老子也要提成
I want a percentage.
你妈妈还能见到奥普拉本尊
And your mama get to meet Oprah.
还有盖尔
And Gayle.
妈妈 你把我搞得紧张死了
Mom, you are stressing me out.
你太小题大做了
You are making this a very big deal,
我还有很多事要做呢
and I got a lot going on.
妈妈 我爱你 爱你
Mom, I love you. Love you.
我也爱你 但你就是不听我说话
Love you, too, but you're not hearing mel
没错 但其他人都听到了
Yes, but everyone else is.
我妈说服我回趟卡尔加里的家
I let my mom talk me into coming home
小住几天看看他们
to Calgary for a quick visit,
突然她给我办了一个盛大的迎婴派对
and suddenly she's throwing me an enormous baby shower
是的 牧师没问题
Oh. Yes, the pastor's fine.
但你把整个教堂的人都喊来了
But the whole congregation?
我也爱你 妈妈
I love you, too, Mommy.
那个女人迟早会要了我的命
That woman is gonna be the death of me.
我告诉她 我不想要迎婴派对
Itold her I did not want a baby shower.
宝宝出生后会需要很多东西
Well, the baby is gonna need a lot of stuff when it comes.
没错 不过为了免费的
Yes, but a free stroller
婴儿车和暖瓶器 不值得让对我
and bottle warmer isn't worth me having to explain
对二十几位老太太解释 说我怎么不小心
to two dozen old ladies how I accidentally
被某个阿猫阿狗把肚子搞大了
let some random dude knock me up
无意冒犯
No offense.
相信我 我知道妈妈们是什么样
Believe me, I know how moms can get.
咋啦 出什么事了
What? What's wrong?
我忘了邀请你妈妈了
I forgot to invite your mom.
明天就是派对了 而且都不是在美国办
The shower's tomorrow, and in another country.
没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
-那你为什么尖叫  -我叫了吗
Then why did you scream? Did I?
我不该叫的
I shouldn't have.
我该怎么办呢
What am I gonna do?
你妈妈永远不会原谅我的
Your mom is never gonna forgive me
老特尼 冷静点 好吗
Courtney, calm down, okay?
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.
她根本不喜欢这种事
This isn't even her kind of thing.
而且还得远赴加拿大
And it's all the way in Canada.
相信我 你是在帮她的忙
Trust me, you are doing her a favor.
现在她不必因为拒绝你 而让你失望了
Now she doesn't have to let you down by saying no.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我当然确定
Of course I'm sure.
你以为我不了解自己的母亲吗
You think I don't know my own mother?
好吧 好吧 你只管
Okay. All right, you just,
你只管去开心开心
you just, you go and- and have fun.
你回来我们再见
And, uh, I'll see you when you get back.
好吧 好吧 谢谢
Okay, okay, thank you.
-好的  -你说什么回来
AlI right. Get back"?
她已经要去吃午饭了吗
Is she going to Iunch already?
不 爸爸 她要回加拿大
No, Dad, she's going to Canada.
她最好一小时内赶回来
Well, she better be back in an hour.
欢迎来到本街区 欢迎来到本社区
Welcome to the block, welcome to the. neighborhood*
欢迎来到这个大家庭
Welcome to the hood.
晚餐太好吃了 珍玛
Dinner was fantastic, Gemma.
牛排做得很完美
The steaks were perfect.
谢谢 蒂娜
Oh, thanks, Tina. Mm- hmm.
卡尔文 喝干邑吗
Calvin, cognac?
瞌睡来枕头了
Ah, you're breaking out the yac.
这段友谊终于有了回报
This friendship is finally paying off.
那么 拉马尔 是我疯了 还是你今晚真的是坐公车来的
So, Lamar, am I crazy, or did you take the bus here tonight?
你没疯 珍玛
You're not crazy, Gemma.
我那辆车着火了
The Datsun caught on fire.
真倒霉
Ah, that's a bummer.
你还买不起新车
And you can't afford to buy another car
因为你找不到工作
because you can't fjnd a job.
你找不到工作 因为他没有车
You can't find a job because he doesn't have a car.
好棘手的问题
It's quite a pickle.
我倒是很乐意给你一份工作
Well, I'd love to give you a job,
但是学校针对雇佣有前科的重罪犯
but the school has a very clear policy
有非常明确的政策
on hiring convicted felons.
那就是不准雇
You can't.
该死的
Damn it.
真希望我们认识一些
Just wish we knew someone
拥有家族企业的朋友
who owned a private business.
好吧
Ah, okay.
拿人手短 喝人嘴短
I see I've been suckered by the'yac.
你们总是说 好人应该
You guys always talk about how good people
有第二次机会
deserve a second chance.
是啊 但我说的不是我去给人机会啊 戴夫
Yes, but not from me, Dave.
再说 我也帮不上忙
Besides, I can't help.
我没有任何岗位空缺
I don't have any openings
不 你有的
Yes, you do.
那个叫洛厄尔的门童今早不是辞职了吗
Didn't Lowell the valet guy just quit this morning?
我都忘了
I had forgotten that.
没错 蒂娜
Yes, Tina.
非常感谢你及时的提醒
Thank you so much for that very timely reminder.
你真的相信妈妈不会在乎自己
Do you really believe Mama wouldn't care if she wasn't
没被迎婴派对邀请吗
invited to the baby shower?
她当然在乎 她会心碎死的
Of course she'd care. She'd be heartbroken.
所以她会永远蒙在鼓里
But that's why she's never going to find out.
真的吗 马蒂
Oh, really, Marty?
考特尼自己都不知道自己怀孕
This is the same woman who knew Courtney was pregnant
咱们这位老妈倒先知道了
before Courtney knew she was pregnant.
我知道 我知道 但这次不一样
I know Tknow, I know, but- but this is different.
迎婴派对远在加拿大
The showerls all the way in Canada.
去的人她一个也不认识
And she don't know nobody who's going.
她又不是有什么魔法
It's not like she has magical powers.
马蒂 迎婴派对
Marty baby shower.
她是个女巫
She's a witch!
我想给考特尼办个迎婴派对
I want to throw Courtney a shower.
我们来谈谈日期吧
Let's talk dates.
日期 没错
Oh, datesl Yeah.
-举办迎婴派对的日期 是的  -是的
For- for a future shower, yes. Yeah.
不 不 不 考特尼不想办
No! No, no, Courtney doesn't
迎婴派对 她讨厌迎婴派对
want a baby shower. She hates showers.
什么人会讨厌迎婴派对啊
What kind of person hates showers?
她是千禧一代 天蝎座 赫奇帕奇学院的
Well, she's a millennial and a Scorpio and a Hufflepuff.
别这样 这会是一个超级有趣的派对
Oh come on itd be a super fun party
大家会送礼物给你
where people give you stuff
我知道 她就是不正常
I know. She's crazy.
这可算是一个里程碑啊
Talk about a milestone.
你永远不会忘记 在自己离散多年的父亲出狱后
You know, you never forget the first day you drop off
你第一天送他去干
your long- lost dad at his minimum- wage job
最低工资的工作
just after he gets out of prison.
就像一首很棒的乡村歌曲
It's like a great country song,
听着 我们说清楚了 拉马尔
Listen, just so we're clear, Lamar,
这里有一些要求
there are a few requirements.
永远保持你的制服干净
AlI right, always keep your uniform clean,
要准时 还有
be on time and
别偷东西
don't steal anything.
收到
Roger that.
卡尔文 你保证过不会对一个
Uh, Calvin, you promised not to be prejudiced
洗心革面的好人抱有有偏见的
against a good man who deserves a second chance,
不 我答应再给他重来的机会
No, I said I'd give him a second chance.
但我没说不会有偏见
I didn't say I wasn't gonna be prejudiced.
哟 马蒂
Yo, Marty.
嘿 你从卡尔加里回来了
Oh, hey. You're back from Calgary.
是的 如释重负啊 太疯狂了
Yes, I am so relieved. It was crazy.
但我挺过来了 宝宝也得到了一大堆很棒的礼物
But I survived, and the baby got a ton of great gifts.
我正好赶上回来参加冷知识问答之夜
And I made it back in time for trivia night.
我们要把那个趾高气昂的
We are going to crush that team
牙科保健师的队伍打的满地找牙 小趴菜
of cocky dental hygienists, the Flossy Posse?
不好意思 你们是不是在说冷知识问答之夜
Sorry, di- uh, did I hear trivia night?
因为我很擅长知识问答
Because I am fantastic at trivia.
我今晚也没啥事 伙计们
And I have no plans tonight, guys.
啥事都没有
Nothing.
大卫
David.
我知道 但我们已经有四个人了
Well, I know, but we already have four.
我 考特尼 马尔科姆和朱利安
Uh, it's me, Courtney, Malcolm and Julian.
给你 老大
Here you go, boss man.
就这个朱利安
That Julian?
是啊
Yeah.
卖咖啡的朱利安
The coffee guy?
他知道无数的冷知识
He knows a million random facts.
没错 朱利安
Yeah. Julian?
五大湖里哪个最小
Bacon Smallest Great Lake.
按水量 伊利湖
By volume, Erie.
按占地 安大略湖
By area, Ontario.
碰个拳 好吧
Give me some, all right.
然而他却在
And yet he wrote
我拿铁杯上写 卡尔闻
"Clavion"on my latte.
嘿 帮我个忙
Oh, hey, do me a favor.
留意一下你家的快递 为什么
Keep an eye out for boxes at your house. Why?
在我住的大楼里经常
Well, people are constantly stealing packages
有人偷快递 所以我把所有的
at my building, so I sent all
迎婴派礼物寄到你家了
the baby shower gifts to your house
好吧
Oh, okay.
快递什么时候到
When are they arriving?
网上信息说
Well, the online registry stuff
应该今天就能陆续送到
should start getting there today.
今天吗 今天这个今天吗
Today? Today, today.
就是此时的今天吗
As as in today.
哦 太方便了
Oh, so convenient.
是的
Yeah
好吧
Okay.
你好呀
Shello?
马尔科姆 没时间跟你闹了
Malcolm, this is no time for shello
考特尼把迎婴派对的礼物寄到了我们家了
Courtney sent the baby shower gifts to our house.
如果被妈妈发现 她会比自己喜欢的女团
When Mom sees it, she's gonna be more upset
解散更难过的
than when En Vogue broke up.
还记得那次她冲到学校来给我们请假吗
Remember she came and got us out of school?
是啊 太糟糕了
Oh, yeah, that was bad.
嘿 别慌
You know what? Hey, do not panic.
好吧 我去看看 小弟
Okay? Let me go check, baby bro.
好吧
Okay.
我得把这些拿进去
I'm gonna get these inside.
好吧 快点 快点
Okay. Hurry, hurry.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
马尔科姆吗 马尔科姆 怎么了
Malcolm? Malcolm, what is it?
你好 马尔科姆
Hello, Malcolm
所以你要我相信 她只是忘记了
So I'm supposed to believe she just forgot
邀请我参加在加拿大举办的秘密迎婴派对吗
to invite me to a secret Canadian baby shower?
是的 夫人
Yes, ma'am
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay
还有 马蒂
And, uh...Marty,
他不想让你知道 因为他觉得
he didn't want you to know because he thought
你可能会 暴走
that you might be...mad.
我没暴走
Oh, Im not mad.
没有吗
You're not?
妈妈 那太好了
Mama, that is good.
我心死了
I'm more numb.
悲伤莫大于心死
Numb with sadness.
很抱歉 妈妈
Iam so sorry, Mama.
我能做什么让你好受点吗
Is there, uh, is there anything I can dp to help?
你可以去找个女孩 把她肚子搞大
You can meet a girl, get her pregnant
然后邀请我参加迎婴派对
and invite me to the baby shower.
我只是想给你买杯冻酸奶什么的
I was thinking more like frozen yogurt.
嗨 卡尔文
Hey, Calvin.
看看我爸 在这里拼命工作
Look at my dad out here busting his hump.
没错
Yes, he is.
虽然我不想承认 但你是对的
I hate to admit it, but you were right.
没错 嘿 我在想
Yeah. Hey, you know, Iwas thinking.
也许我们该请你和蒂娜
Maybe we should take you and Tina
今晚去厄尼酒吧喝酒
out to drinks at Ernie's tonight.
庆祝一下我爸爸工作一切顺利
You know, celebrate how well this is all going.
你就是为了说一句 我早告诉过你吧
Is this just so you can say, I told you so"?
是啊 差不多吧
Yeah, well, pretty much.
好吧 要是你买单的话
Well, if you're buying,
你想说什么就说什么吧
you can say whatever you want.
如果你爸爸继续保持这个状态
And if your dad keeps working like this,
他会成为本月最佳员工
he's gonna be employee of the month.
最佳员工能得到什么奖励
What, uh, does employee of the month get?
奖励是下个月不被炒鱿鱼
They get to work another month.
好极了
Good enough.
她不生气吗
She wasn't mad?
不 我倒希望她生气
No, I wish.
她是很伤心
She was sad.
不 太糟糕了
Oh, no, that's bad.
好吧 好吧 我是这么想的
Okay, okay, here's what I'm thinking.
碰上这种问题 也许你选择无视 自然就
This is one of those problems that just goes away
烟消云散
if you avoid it.
就像检查引擎的提示灯亮了不用管一样
Like the "check engine" light.
好吧 我觉得你的回答是在嘲笑我
Okay, feel like you're mocking me with that answer.
但确实没错
But yes.
马蒂 如果考特尼发现你撒谎了怎么办
Marty, what if Courtney finds out you lied?
你跟她说 妈妈不会在乎迎婴派对
You told her Mama wouldn't care about the shower.
妈妈和考特尼很少见面
Mom and Courtney barely see each other.
她怎么会知道呢
How's she gonna find out?
在我的脑海里
Well, off the top of my head,
想到了一种可能
I can think of one way.
等一下 牌子上是不是写着
Wait a mrnute, does that sign say- ?
今天是冷知识问答之夜吗
Is it trivia night?
天啊
Oh, God.
伙计们 我们应该一起玩
Guys, we should play.
我开始觉得这是戴夫的另一个圈套了
This is starting to feel like another Dave setup.
我下圈套下得越来越好了 对吧
I'm getting good at them, right?
妈妈
Mommy.
我很高兴见到你
I am so glad to see you,
因为当我告诉你
because when I told you
考特尼不办迎婴派对的时候
that Courtney wasn't having a baby shower,
我以为你是指在这个国家
I just assumed you meant in this country.
加拿大的迎婴派对完全不同
Canadian showers are completely different.
就像他们有自己的感恩节一样
It's like how they have their own Thanksgiving,
只不过是在另一天 所以没人在乎
but it's on a different day, so nobody cares.
没事的 马蒂
It's fine, Marty.
真的吗
It is?
真的
Yes.
我今天想明白了很多
I got a lot of clarity today
我知道我永远不会成为我孙子生活的一部分
I know that I will never be a part of my grardchild's life.
现在我还知道了你说的话毫无意义
And I now know that your wprd means nothing.
不 这可不好
No, w- - that is not fine.
-妈妈  -嘿 马蒂
Mommy...Hey, Marty.
-你好 巴太太  -你不用叫我巴太太
Hi, Mrs. B. Oh, you don't have to call me Mrs. B.
叫我路人甲就可以了
Just call me"random lady,
因为对我孙子来说 我永远都是路人甲
because that's all I'll ever be to my grandchild.
好了 你们这些醉鬼 现在是问答时间
AlI right, you drunken brainiacs, it's trivia timel
马蒂 你妈妈为什么生我的气
Marty, why is your mom mad at me?
嗯 那是 是一个
Well, that'sa...it's a quagmire
谜中的谜语
in sort of an enigma,
包裹在一个谜的内部
inside of a conundrum.
非常棘手的问题
It's a toughie.
最后一轮问题
And final question of the round.
每答对一个问题得一分
One point for every correct answer.
说出惰性气体的名称
Name the noble gases.
-哦 惰性气体 我们可以的  -是的
Oh, noble gases? We got this. Yeah.
-我真不敢相信你 马蒂  -考特尼 拜托了
I can't believe you, Marty. Courtney, please.
嘿 嘿 嘿 伙计们 我们能专心点吗
Hey, hey, hey, guys, guys, can we please focus?
我们需要一些答案
We need some answers.
我需要一些答案
I need some answers.
你为什么告诉我你妈妈
Why did you tell me your mom would be fine
不去迎婴礼会没问题
not going to the shower?
因为我想让大家都开心
Because I was trying to make everyone happy.
哦 那么 干得好 看看大家多开心
Oh, then, well done. Look how happy everyone is.
氩
DAVE: Argon,
氡 氪 氮
radon, krypton, oganesson.
就这些
Got them all.
戴夫 你能冷静点吗
GEMMA: Dave, would you chill?
你没看到蒂娜有多难过吗
Can't you see how emotional Tina is?
看到了 但你知道怎样能让她感觉好点 获胜
Yes, uh, but you know what would make her feel better? Winning.
卡尔文 第四问
Calvjn, uh, number four.
你确定这些都是70年代
Are you sure that these are all
帕姆·格里尔的电影吗
the Pam Grier movies of the 1970s?
戴夫 我告诉过你 我了解帕姆·格里尔
Dave, I told you, I know my Pam Grier.
就是我 帕姆和我的录像机
It was me, Pam and my VCR.
我们有过一段渊源呢
We had a thang.
那是一种友谊
It was a friendship.
时间到 放下铅笔
And that's time. Pencils down.
看看
Look at this.
这真是翻车现场
It's a damn travesty.
马蒂 我们有五个题空白
Marty, we got five blank questions, man.
考特尼让我分心了
Courtney was distracting me.
你可以随便编几个答案啊 马蒂
You could have just made up some answers, Marty.
显然 说谎是你的专长
Apparently, lies are your specialty.
我不得不沉浸进一个非常黑暗的地方
And I had to go to a real dark place
才能说出所有这些连环杀手的名字
to name all these serial killers.
结果为了什么
And for what?
马蒂 我们得做点什么
Marty, we need to do something about this.
好吧 别担心
Okay, don't worry.
我有办法
I have a solution.
我们就把孩子给她吧
We just give her the baby.
我是不会把我孩子给你妈的
I'm not giving your mom my baby.
好的 嗯 你这样说的话
Okay, yeah, when you say it like that, of course
我可能是椰林飘香鸡尾酒喝多了
This, uh, might be the skinny pina colada talking,
但是 你们逊爆了
but, uh, you guys blow.
来吧 戴夫 我们的车来了
Come on, Dave, our rideshare is here.
-我们得回家找格罗弗了  -哦 格罗弗
We got to get home to Grover. Ooh, Grover.
毛茸茸的蓝色布偶 1970年在《芝麻街》首次亮相
Furry blue Muppet, debuted on Sesame Street in 1970.
还是我比较牛
Booyah.
我打赌你没想到今晚会有冷知识竞赛优胜者
I bet you didn't expect to have trivia winners
上你的车 对吧
in your car tonight, huh?
是的 我确实喝了椰林飘香
And, yes, I did have a pina colada.
问我有没有付钱 你可以问我
Ask me if I paid for it. You can ask me.
-好了 戴夫 戴夫 冷静下来  -问我 呃 先生
Okay, Dave, Dave. Calm down. Ask me. Uh, sir?
先生 先生 我选的是健谈版司机 我想和你聊聊
Sir, sir, I requested a chatty driver, and I'd like to chat.
今晚很不错吧
Nice night, huh?
-爸  -拉马尔
Dad? Lamar?
从哪儿弄来的这辆车
Where did you get this car?
借来的
It's a loaner.
这是保险盒子的车吗
Is this one of the Fusebox cars?
现在你开始草率下结论了
Well, now you're just jumping to conclusions.
草率吗
Am I?
这些是保险盒子的地板垫
These are Fusebox floor mats.
我不想把车弄脏
I didn't want to get the car dirty.
不把车弄成赃车的一个好方法就是不要偷车
A good way to not get it dirty would be not to steal it.
偷车
Steal it?
孩子们称之为“副业”
The kids call it a side hustle. "
车主自己把钥匙交给了我
The owner literally handed me the keys
并告诉我要好好保管
and told me to take good care of it.
我想他没有打算用它来拉乘客的
I don't think he meant to pick up passengers in it.
你那是没听到他说话的语气
You didn't hear the way he said it.
怎么了
What happened?
我不知道 车自己停了下来
I don't know. The car just stopped.
为什么
Why?
别问我 这不是我的车
Don't ask me. It's not my car.
你上次充电是什么时候
When was the last time you charged it?
你知道吗 我一直想查查
You know, I've been meaning to look up
一般该多久充一次电来着
how often you got to do that.
早上好 卡尔文
Hey, morning, Calvin.
我只是来送你最喜欢的新员工的
Just, uh, dropping off your new favorite employee.
嗯 嘿 拉马尔
Yeah. Hey, Lamar
我们昨天修的银色现代
the silver Hyundai we worked on yesterday,
只充了一半电
it's only half charged.
充电器肯定坏了
Hmm, uh, charger must be broken.
嗯 我猜就是这样
Yeah, I bet that's what it is.
我肯定是这样的 必须是这样的
Im sure that's what it is. Has to be what it is.
手机充电器是这样 汽车充电器也是这样
Happens to phone chargers, happens to car chargers.
结案
Case closed.
我们不是对所有充电器
Well- well, didn't we run diagnostics
-都做了诊断吗  -那在这种情况下
on all of the chargers? Well, in that case,
可能是其他东西 可能是其他任何东西的问题
could be something else, could be anything else.
可能有八万种原因 是的
Could be a million things. Yeah.
坦率地说 这是一个可能永远无法解开的谜
It is a mystery that, frankly, may never be solved.
事实上 我们别努力解谜了
In fact, we might as well stop trying.
是的 你绝对应该闭嘴了
Yeah, you should definitely stop.
拉马尔 你能帮我把那辆现代车插到另一个充电器上吗
Lamar, would you please plug the Hyundai up to another charger?
没问题 老板 谢谢
You got it, boss. Thank you.
谢谢你替我打掩护
Thanks for covering for me.
你是个好儿子
You're a good son.
也许吧 但我不是个好朋友
Yeah, maybe, but Im a terrible friend.
这是我第一次对卡尔文撒谎
You know, that's the first time I've ever lied to Calvin.
我是说除了那次我跟他说他的西班牙凉菜汤
I mean, except for the time that I told him his gazpacho
不太咸
wasn't too salty.
其实盐王爷都咸死了
It was inedible.
就像吃了一碗海洋
It was like eating a bowl of ocean,
嘿 妈
Hey, Mom?
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
能啊
Sure.
我只是在看家庭录像 当年的一切都很简单
Just watching home movies, when things were simple.
只有我和妈妈的小宝贝
Just me and Mama's little babies.
学校话剧里的那个是马蒂吗
Is that Marty in the school play?
是的 他表现特别差 他就只是呆站在那里
Yeah. He was terrible. He just stood there.
我是在扮演一棵树
I was playing a tree.
好吧 妈妈
Okay. Mom? Uh...
我想让你知道我有多抱歉
I need you to know how sorry I am.
好吧 整件事都是我的错
Okay? This whole thing was all my fault.
不 不是的 马蒂
No, it's not, Marty.
这一切都是因为我犯了一个愚蠢的错误
It all started because I made an awful, stupid mistake,
忘了邀请你
forgetting to invite you.
伤害了你的感情
It hurt your feelings,
我很抱歉
and I am so sorry.
我想我应该多体谅你一点
I guess I could have been a little more understanding.
我知道有了孩子的大脑是什么样的
I know what baby brain is like.
有一次我搞混了
One time, I got confused
把母乳倒进了卡尔文的咖啡里
and put breast milk in Calvin's coffee.
-哕  -他很喜欢的
Ew. He loved it.
但就是这样
But that's it exactly.
我脑子不清不楚的
I'm so scattered.
我把一切都搞砸了
I'm screwing up left and right.
但我不只是想让你成为孩子生活的一部分
But I don't just want you to be a part of this baby's life.
我需要你
I need you.
真的吗
You do?
真的 我妈妈远在2000英里之外
I do. My mom is 2, 000 miles away.
嗯 我们都要全职工作
MARTY: Yeah, and we're both gonna be working full- time,
所以我们需要有人来照顾这个孩子
so we gonna need somebody to dump this baby on.
你们愿意把孩子丢给我啊
You'd dump that baby on me?
蒂娜
Tina?
现在没空 珍玛
Not now, Gemma!
但这是紧急情况
Uh, but it's an emergency
我炉子上的肉汁有大块结团
I've got clumpy gravy on the stove
我不知道该怎么办
and I don't know what to do.
珍玛 我们不是说好了你再也别做肉汁了吗
Gemma, I thought we agreed you would never attempt gravy again.
你不具备成功的条件
You don't have what it takes.
好吧 在你说别的任何伤人的话之前
Okay, before you say anything else hurtful.
惊喜
ALL: Surprise!
咋回事儿
What is happening?
-这是迎婴派对  -事实上
It's a baby shower Well, actually,
这是专门为我们孩子的蒂娜奶奶办的
it's a grandma shower for our baby s Glammy T.
那就是我呢
That's me.
-给  -天呐 噢
Here you go. Oh, my God- oh
我知道我之前说过原谅你 但我是骗你的
Look, I know I said I forgave you earlier, but I was lying.
现在我真的原谅你了
Now I forgive you.
让我偷一个吧
Ooh, let me steal one of these.
-他知道了  -谁
He knows. Who?
卡尔文 他盯上我们了
Calvin. He's on to us.
我拿着一盘面包卷香肠从他身边走过
I walked past him with a tray of pigs in a blanket,
他说“让我偷一个吧”
and he said, "Let me steal one of those. "
好像没啥关系
Seems pretty innocent.
打扰一下 天啊
Excuse me. Oh, man.
这些东西太好吃了 好吃到犯罪
These things are so good, man, they should be a crime.
也不是很好吃
They're not that good.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
别再折磨我了
Stop toying with me.
天啊 你就像只猫 我就像你的盘中餐
God, you're like a cat, and I'm like your little mouse.
儿子 没事的 他是深感内疚
Son, it's okay. He's racked with guilt.
卡尔文 你知道那辆没充上电的车吧
Calvin, you know that car that wasn't charged?
因为我昨晚开着它去拉客了
It's because I drove it for a ridesharing service last night.
什么 你从保险盒子里拿了客户的车出去载人
Whoa, whoa. You took a customer's car from the Fusebox?
你要明白 我很想赚钱
You got to understand, I'm desperate to make money
这样我就能多来这里
so I can come around more.
我刚找回我的家人 我不想失去他们
I- I just got my family back and I don't want to lose them.
但我让戴夫对你撒谎了
But I told Dave to lie to you about it,
为此 我很抱歉
and for that, I'm sorry.
但你不为偷车的事感到抱歉吗
Oh, but you're not sorry about the grand theft auto?
那 也抱歉 吧
That, too?
我很抱歉 卡尔文
Look, I'm sorry, Calvin.
戴夫 我从来不知道你还是个骗子
You know, Dave, I've never known you to be a liar.
我是说 你这人很复杂
I mean, you've been a lot of other things.
你烦人 讨厌
A nuisance, a pest,
恼人精 嘴里叭叭个不停 衣品也烂
a pain in the ass, an overtalker, a bad dresser.
但我知道如果你撒谎了
But I know if you lied, then,
那一定是有重要的原因
it must have been for an important reason.
确实有
It was.
好吧 我想这一次
AlI right, I guess this one time,
我就不去想这事儿了
I'm just gonna look past it.
我还能继续在这儿工作是吗
So I can keep my job?
哦 不 你被炒了
Oh, no. You're fired.
只是我不会报警的
I'm just not gonna call the police.
好吧 好的 谢谢
Okay. Well, thank you.
但我告诉你哈 我知道
But I tell you what, I know for a fact
马伦哥的汽车男孩那边在招人
that Motor Boys on Marengo, they're hiring.
我很乐意给你写一封
And I would be more than happy to write you
热情洋溢的推荐信
a glowing recommendation.
你真的愿意为我写推荐信吗
You'd do that for me?
不是
No.
他这么做是为了我
He's doing it for me.
不是
No.
我这么做是因为我讨厌汽车男孩
I'm doing it because I hate Motor Boys.
尽情地去偷他家的东西吧
Feel free to steal everything under the roof.
我会的
I will.
让我们来看看啊
Let's see.
哦 太美好了
Oh, so sweet.
现在我不用自己说了
Now Idon't have to say it.
是的 啊
Yeah. Aww.
太可爱了
So cute. Mm- hmml
蒂娜奶奶
Glammy T?
下一个开这个 哦
Open this one next. Ooh.
天哪
Oh, my goodness.
Ah! How cute.
亲子运动鞋
Matching sneakers!
我以前见过妈妈大哭特哭 但是马蒂啊
You know, I've seen Mama ugly- cry before, but Marty?
嗯 他是他妈妈的乖儿子嘛
Well, he is his mama's boy.